Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
Keumbok.
كيومس.
See you again.
أراك مرة أخرى.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
This is my first time making a friend in Seoul.
هذه هي المرة الأولى التي أتعرف فيها على صديق في سيول.
Not as a friend.
ليس كصديق.
What?
ماذا؟
I'm asking you out on a date.
أنا أدعوك للخروج في موعد.
Dr. Ji?
الدكتور جي؟
There's a mark.
هناك علامة.
Dr. Ji!
الدكتور جي!
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
What?
ماذا؟
You're nothing but strength, as always.
أنت لست سوى القوة، كما هو الحال دائمًا.
Jigwi?
هل هذا يساعد؟
Dr. Ji, a-are you okay?
الدكتور جي، هل أنت بخير؟
Your hand is bleeding.
يدك تنزف.
You probably scratched it when you fell.
ربما خدشته عندما سقطت.
Go home and apply some medicine—
اذهب إلى المنزل واستخدم بعض الأدوية
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
I've always known he's old-fashioned and cruel.
لقد عرفت دائمًا أنه قديم الطراز وقاسي.
Oh, right.
أوه، صحيح.
You said you two were friends, right?
قلت أنكما صديقان، أليس كذلك؟
Friends?
أصدقاء؟
Don't be fooled by him.
لا تنخدع به.
Jigwi once
جيغوي مرة واحدة
stabbed Bihyung in his chest.
طعن بيهيونغ في صدره.
S-Stabbed?
طعنة؟
Don't mess with Keumbok.
لا تعبث مع Keumbok.
Do you like him?
هل تحبه؟
Yes.
نعم.
What?
ماذا؟
No, it's not like that.
لا، ليس الأمر كذلك.
In that case, Keumbok, do you dislike me?
في هذه الحالة، كيمبوك، هل تكرهني؟
No, that's not it.
لا، ليس هذا هو الأمر.
What he's asking is if there's something special between us.
ما يسأل عنه هو إذا كان هناك شيء خاص بيننا.
You...
أنت...
are someone special to me, that's true.
هل أنت شخص مميز بالنسبة لي، هذا صحيح.
That's not it.
هذا ليس هو.
What he means is someone you really cherish
ما يعنيه هو شخص عزيز عليك حقًا
and is so special that you'd risk your life for—
وهي خاصة جدًا لدرجة أنك قد تخاطر بحياتك من أجلها
That's right!
هذا صحيح!
I really cherish you, and you're very special to me.
أنا حقا أعتز بك، وأنت خاص جدا بالنسبة لي.
Of course I'd risk my life for you.
بالطبع سأخاطر بحياتي من أجلك.
Huh?
هاه؟
That's my first time hearing this...
هذه هي المرة الأولى التي أسمع فيها هذا...
Didn't you know?
ألم تعلم؟
It's been like this since I first met you.
لقد كان الأمر هكذا منذ أن التقيت بك لأول مرة.
I'll borrow this.
سأستعير هذا.
Well...
حسنًا...
Let's talk about the things we didn't get to next time.
دعونا نتحدث عن الأشياء التي لم نتمكن من التطرق إليها في المرة القادمة.
Keep in touch.
أبق على اتصال.
What? Wait—
ماذا؟ انتظر—
I must have lived for too long.
لا بد وأنني عشت لفترة طويلة جدًا.
He'd risk his life?
هل يخاطر بحياته؟
What a pain.
يا له من ألم!
[The Story of Bihyung]
[قصة بيهيونغ]
[Hwang Jaewook]
[هوانغ جايووك]
[Lee Chamin]
[لي شامين]
[Kang Chanwoo]
[كانغ تشان وو]
[Nam Taekjun]
[نام تايكجون]
[Seo Heesun]
[هذا هو هيسون]
[The Story of Bihyung]
[قصة بيهيونغ]
Aren't you two close?
هل أنتم قريبين من بعضكما؟
We used to be.
لقد كنا كذلك.
Until he betrayed Bihyung.
حتى خان بيهيونغ.
What did he do?
ماذا فعل؟
Without Bihyung around, I'm afraid I can't say much.
بدون بيهيونغ حولي، أخشى أنني لا أستطيع أن أقول الكثير.
But because of this, Bihyung had to endure a lot of pain for a long time.
ولكن بسبب هذا، كان على بيهيونج أن يتحمل الكثير من الألم لفترة طويلة.
Speaking of,
وبالحديث عن ذلك،
what's this on your face?
ما هذا على وجهك؟
I got it while catching a ghost.
لقد حصلت عليه أثناء اصطياد شبح.
What?
ماذا؟
You can catch ghosts?
هل يمكنك اصطياد الأشباح؟
As expected of a sorcerer.
كما هو متوقع من الساحر.
That's amazing.
هذا مدهش.
Bihyung ordered me to do it.
بيهيونغ أمرني أن أفعل ذلك.
He said something about a kid who's afraid of walking at night.
قال شيئًا عن طفل يخاف من المشي في الليل.
Do you know who that kid is?
هل تعرف من هو هذا الطفل؟
Kid?
طفل؟
Hey.
يا.
Can I hold onto you?
هل يمكنني التمسك بك؟
It's night, after all.
إنه الليل، بعد كل شيء.
Are you a kid? Why are you so scared?
هل أنت طفل؟ لماذا أنت خائف هكذا؟
You have my energy on you, so you'll be fine for a while.
لقد حصلت على طاقتي، لذلك سوف تكون بخير لفترة من الوقت.
Even so...
مع ذلك...
You're faster than me, since you have long legs.
أنت أسرع مني، لأن لديك ساقين طويلتين.
Oh, that's...
أوه، هذا...
Be quiet.
كن هادئاً.
Oh.
أوه.
It's safe in the neighborhood at night, too.
ومن الآمن في الحي ليلاً أيضًا.
Just letting you know.
فقط أريد أن أعلمك.
Wash up and come out.
اغتسل وخرج.
We're having Cheonggukjang for dinner today.
سنتناول تشيونغ جوكجانغ على العشاء اليوم.
Really?
حقًا؟
Then I'll have one more bowl.
ثم سآخذ وعاء آخر.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
You haven't changed.
لم تتغير.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
I'm healthy, but I don't have any money.
أنا بصحة جيدة، ولكن ليس لدي أي أموال.
I'll buy insurance next time...
سأشتري التأمين في المرة القادمة...
Oh, no!
أوه لا!
I'm calling you after seeing your photo on the Aspiring Actor Forum.
اتصل بك بعد رؤية صورتك في منتدى الممثل الطموح.
What?
ماذا؟
You're Ha Keumbok, right?
أنت ها كومبوك، أليس كذلك؟
Yes, that's me!
نعم، هذا أنا!
Ah!
اه!
-Ah! -Ha Keumbok!
-آه! -إلى كيمبوك!
What should I do?
ماذا علي أن أفعل؟
About what?
عن ما؟
I was chosen!
لقد تم اختياري!
But why is your heart beating so fast?
ولكن لماذا ينبض قلبك بهذه السرعة؟
Are you sick?
هل انت مريض؟
Article 4.
المادة 4.
Article 4, Article 4!
المادة 4، المادة 4!
Article 4 of the contract!
المادة 4 من العقد!
"Do not approach suddenly."
"لا تقترب فجأة."
I'm really sorry.
انا آسف حقا.
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
Well...
حسنًا...
-An agency?
-وكالة؟
I uploaded my photo on the Aspiring Actors Forum,
لقد قمت برفع صورتي على منتدى الممثلين الطموحين،
and this agency said that they liked it
وقالت هذه الوكالة أنها أعجبت بها
and asked me to pay them a visit.
وطلبوا مني أن أقوم بزيارتهم.
You can convince people with just one photo.
يمكنك إقناع الناس بصورة واحدة فقط.
You're amazing, Keumbok.
أنت مدهش، كيمبوك.
It's nothing.
لا شئ.
Would you like to have a look?
هل ترغب في إلقاء نظرة؟
Here.
هنا.
Well...
حسنًا...
Wow, that's amazing.
واو، هذا مدهش.
Can I print this and hang it up in a frame?
هل يمكنني طباعة هذا وتعليقه في إطار؟
It's not quite at that level.
إنه ليس على هذا المستوى تماما.
At this level, I don't think we need to work in the through the night.
على هذا المستوى، لا أعتقد أننا بحاجة إلى العمل طوال الليل.
It should be able to repel ghosts.
يجب أن يكون قادرًا على صد الأشباح.
It has such a scary vibe.
إنها تمتلك مثل هذا الشعور المخيف.
I haven't felt this much pressure in a long time.
لم أشعر بهذا القدر من الضغط منذ وقت طويل.
Stop looking at it.
توقف عن النظر إليه.
I'm in this photo too though.
أنا في هذه الصورة أيضًا.
[Dr. Jigwi: What are you doing?]
[دكتور جيغوي: ماذا تفعل؟]
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
[Dr. Jigwi: I miss you.]
[الدكتور جيغوي: أفتقدك.]
I miss you.
أفتقدك.
Hyung, is there something wrong?
هيونغ، هل هناك شيء خاطئ؟
Oh.
أوه.
No.
لا.
You look much better in person than in photos.
أنت تبدو أفضل بكثير في الواقع من الصور.
You have fair skin
لديك بشرة فاتحة
and bright eyes.
وعيون مشرقة.
Even so, you're not saying anything like I'm handsome.
مع ذلك، فأنت لا تقول شيئًا مثل أنني وسيم.
He has high standards.
لديه معايير عالية.
He lives his life looking at me every day,
إنه يعيش حياته وهو ينظر إلي كل يوم،
so it'd be weird if he didn't have high standards.
لذا سيكون الأمر غريبًا إذا لم تكن لديه معايير عالية.
Bihyung is not my type.
بيهيونغ ليس نوعي المفضل.
What?
ماذا؟
Y-You have a type?
س-هل لديك نوع؟
I have standards, too.
لدي معايير أيضا.
I'm curious.
أنا فضولي.
What's your ideal type?
ما هو نوعك المثالي؟
Someone ordinary.
شخص عادي.
Pale skin
بشرة شاحبة
and full lips.
وشفتين ممتلئتين.
With thin ankles, but is a fast runner.
مع كاحليه الرفيعين، لكنه عداء سريع.
Wow, you're so picky.
واو، أنت صعب الإرضاء للغاية.
What?
ماذا؟
Everyone has standards like that, don't they?
هل كل شخص لديه معايير مثل هذه ؟
Well, my ideal type is clear, too.
حسنًا، نوعي المثالي واضح أيضًا.
You two haven't even dated before.
لم تواعدا بعضكما من قبل.
That's not true.
هذا ليس صحيحا.
I was invited on a date recently—
لقد تمت دعوتي إلى موعد مؤخرًا
When? Where? With whom?
متى؟ أين؟ مع من؟
Answer me with the 5Ws and 1H.
أجبني باستخدام 5Ws و 1H.
But it sounded like a joke.
لكن الأمر بدا وكأنه مزحة.
I knew it.
كنت أعرف.
You're Ha Keumpoop, after all.
أنت ها كومبوب، بعد كل شيء.
What?
ماذا؟
Gosh, I'm doomed.
يا إلهي، لقد حُكم علي بالهلاك.
Well...
حسنًا...
The agency sent me the script for the meeting in advance.
لقد أرسلت لي الوكالة نص الاجتماع مسبقًا.
The lines are all for romance scenes.
الخطوط كلها للمشاهد الرومانسية.
What's wrong with that?
ما الخطأ في ذلك؟
You may find this unbelievable...
ربما تجد هذا أمرًا لا يصدق...
but I've never been in a relationship.
ولكنني لم أكن في علاقة أبدًا.
Are you laughing?
هل تضحك؟
Why do you keep making me conscious of you?
لماذا تستمر في جعلني واعيا بك؟
Y-Y-You've gone crazy!
YY-لقد جننت!
This is just the beginning.
هذه مجرد البداية.
I won't forgive you. I'm going to report you to the police.
لن أسامحك، سأبلغ عنك للشرطة.
J-Just for this?
ج-فقط لهذا؟
To register our marriage. [T/N: A pun on "reporting to the police" and "registering a marriage" in Korean.]
لتسجيل زواجنا. [ملاحظة: تورية على "الإبلاغ للشرطة" و"تسجيل الزواج" في اللغة الكورية.]
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
It's cute.
إنه لطيف.
That won't do.
هذا لن يفعل.
This should be a charismatic confession from a man like an injured lone wolf.
يجب أن يكون هذا اعترافًا كاريزميًا من رجل مثل الذئب المنفرد المصاب.
Charismatic?
كاريزمية؟
That's what I'm best at.
هذا ما أنا الأفضل فيه.
Should I just kick them out?
هل يجب علي أن أطردهم؟
H-Hyung, this is a bit...
هـ-هيونغ، هذا قليلاً...
Don't move. Stand at attention!
لا تتحرك. قف منتبهًا!
Huh?
هاه؟
Get a grip and stand at attention!
تمسك بالموقف و قف منتبهًا!
Why do you keep making me conscious of you?
لماذا تستمر في جعلني واعيا بك؟
Are you not going to answer me?
هل لن تجيبني؟
Y-You've gone crazy!
ن-لقد جننت!
I'll show you what "crazy" really is.
سأريكم ما هو "الجنون" حقًا.
I won't forgive you.
لن اسامحك
I'm going to report you to the police.
سأبلغ عنك للشرطة.
To register our marriage.
لتسجيل زواجنا.
How was that?
كيف كان ذلك؟
Did your heart flutter?
هل خفق قلبك؟
I feel like my heart is going to explode.
أشعر وكأن قلبي سينفجر.
Is this what charisma is like?
هل هذه هي الكاريزما؟
How can I do it like you?
كيف يمكنني أن أفعل ذلك مثلك؟
I didn't do anything special.
لم أفعل أي شيء خاص.
It must be a talent of mine.
لا بد أن تكون موهبتي.
I knew it.
كنت أعرف.
Then you must be very popular.
إذن يجب أن تكون مشهورًا جدًا.
Even as a man, my heart is pounding.
حتى كرجل، قلبي ينبض بقوة.
No.
لا.
I'm just like you.
أنا مثلك تماما.
Huh? In what way?
هاه؟ بأي طريقة؟
Have you never dated before?
هل لم تواعد من قبل؟
Since you were born?
منذ ولادتك؟
There's no need for that.
ليس هناك حاجة لذلك .
Who gets into a relationship because it's a necessity?
من يدخل في علاقة لأنها ضرورة؟
Then why do people do it?
إذن لماذا يفعل الناس ذلك؟
It happens when you get curious about someone
يحدث ذلك عندما تشعر بالفضول تجاه شخص ما
and just keep wanting to see them.
وأستمر في الرغبة في رؤيتهم.
Huh?
هاه؟
Have you never met someone like that?
هل لم تقابل شخصًا مثله أبدًا؟
No matter how many times you see them, you still miss them.
بغض النظر عن عدد المرات التي تراهم فيها، فإنك لا تزال تفتقدهم.
Even when you're with them, you still miss them. That's what people say.
حتى وأنت معهم، ما زلت تفتقدهم. هذا ما يقوله الناس.
Some people say it's like being struck by lightning.
يقول بعض الناس أنها مثل ضربة البرق.
Wait...
انتظر...
So...
لذا...
The feeling I felt when you were shouting at me just now...
الشعور الذي شعرت به عندما كنت تصرخ في وجهي للتو...
Can't you even tell the difference between your heart fluttering and fear?
هل لا تستطيع حتى معرفة الفرق بين خفقان قلبك والخوف؟
You can at least avoid a lightning strike.
يمكنك على الأقل تجنب ضربة البرق.
He's looking down on us just because he's dated before.
إنه ينظر إلينا بازدراء فقط لأنه كان على علاقة سابقة.
Looks like it'll be difficult on our own.
يبدو أن الأمر سيكون صعبًا بمفردنا.
Gildal, you're finally starting to realize—
جيلدال، أنت بدأت تدرك أخيرًا-
Instead...
بدلاً من...
you can just teach him.
يمكنك فقط تعليمه.
What?
ماذا؟
You're the only one with experience between us.
أنت الوحيد الذي لديه الخبرة بيننا.
With dating.
مع المواعدة.
I love kimchi soup and kimchi stew the most.
أنا أحب حساء الكيمتشي وحساء الكيمتشي أكثر من أي شيء آخر.
As for snacks, I like red bean porridge the most.
أما بالنسبة للوجبات الخفيفة، فأنا أحب عصيدة الفاصولياء الحمراء أكثر من غيرها.
This is made with precious, self-farmed red beans my grandpa sent.
يتم صنع هذا الطبق باستخدام الفاصوليا الحمراء الثمينة التي زرعتها بنفسي والتي أرسلها لي جدي.
You can't buy these at the supermarket.
لا يمكنك شراء هذه الأشياء من السوبر ماركت.
The rice balls are super soft, aren't they?
كرات الأرز ناعمة جدًا، أليس كذلك؟
It's 'cause they're handmade.
لأنها مصنوعة يدويا.
I heard you're obsessed with red beans— I mean—
سمعت أنك مهووس بالفاصوليا الحمراء - أعني -
I prepared some because I heard you liked them.
لقد قمت بإعداد بعض منها لأنني سمعت أنك تحبها.
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
Well, I'll make do with this.
حسنًا، سأكتفي بهذا.
That's great.
هذا عظيم.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
I heard that if I want to audition for a movie,
سمعت أنه إذا كنت أرغب في إجراء اختبار أداء لفيلم،
I need an agency.
أحتاج إلى وكالة.
Please help me.
من فضلك ساعدني.
Why should I?
لماذا يجب علي ذلك؟
Fine, then.
حسنا إذن.
I'll throw it away.
سأرميها بعيدا.
W-Wait.
W-انتظر.
Hey. Why are you trying so hard just to be an actor?
مهلا، لماذا تحاول جاهدا أن تكون ممثلا فقط؟
I just want to keep the promise I made with my parents when I was young.
أريد فقط أن أحافظ على الوعد الذي قطعته لوالديّ عندما كنت صغيراً.
What?
ماذا؟
I made a promise with them before they passed away.
لقد قطعت لهم وعدًا قبل رحيلهم.
When I become an actor,
عندما أصبح ممثلاً،
I'll make my debut in a movie directed by their favorite director.
سأقوم بأول ظهور لي في فيلم من إخراج مخرجهم المفضل.
Don't you hate them?
ألا تكرههم؟
What?
ماذا؟
They left first
لقد غادروا أولا
and left you all alone.
وترككم وحدكم.
Well... I was still very young.
حسنًا... كنت لا أزال صغيرًا جدًا.
[A rear-end accident caused two deaths in a family.]
[تسبب حادث تصادم خلفي في وفاة شخصين في عائلة واحدة.]
Grandpa.
جدي.
When are my parents coming?
متى سيأتي والدي؟
Leaving such a young child all alone.
ترك طفل صغير وحيدًا.
What am I going to do...
ماذا سأفعل...
[A rear-end accident caused two deaths in a family.]
[تسبب حادث تصادم خلفي في وفاة شخصين في عائلة واحدة.]
Keumbok...
كيمبوك...
And I never thought I was left behind.
ولم أفكر أبدًا أنني تركت خلفًا.
After all, we had so many good memories.
بعد كل شيء، كان لدينا الكثير من الذكريات الجميلة.
If we only remember the people we cherish with sadness,
إذا تذكرنا فقط الأشخاص الذين نعتز بهم بحزن،
it would be so difficult.
سيكون الأمر صعبًا جدًا.
Besides, I still have Grandpa by my side.
وبالإضافة إلى ذلك، لا يزال جدي بجانبي.
Ha Keumdong.
ها كومدونج.
What can I do for you?
ما الذي يمكنني أن أفعله من أجلك؟
Is it good?
هل هو جيد؟
Yes.
نعم.
That kind of feeling where you're curious and you miss them.
هذا النوع من الشعور حيث تشعر بالفضول وتفتقدهم.
[Dr. Jigwi: What are you doing?]
[دكتور جيغوي: ماذا تفعل؟]
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
[Dr. Jigwi: I miss you.]
[الدكتور جيغوي: أفتقدك.]
I miss you.
أفتقدك.
In other words, Jigwi wants to date Keumbok.
بعبارة أخرى، جيجوي يريد مواعدة كيمبوك.
But to Bihyung, Jigwi is...
ولكن بالنسبة لبي هيونغ، جيغوي هو...
-Bihyung, is your stomach feeling better? -Where is Keumpoop?
-بي هيونغ، هل تشعر بتحسن في معدتك؟ -أين كومبوب؟
He said he went to work.
وقال أنه ذهب إلى العمل.
-I was invited on a date recently— -What?
-لقد تمت دعوتي إلى موعد مؤخرًا- -ماذا؟
When? Where? With whom?
متى؟ أين؟ مع من؟
Answer me with the 5Ws and 1H.
أجبني باستخدام 5Ws و 1H.
If this continues, and they fight like they did before...
إذا استمر هذا الأمر، وقاتلوا كما فعلوا من قبل...
I have to stop this!
يجب أن أوقف هذا!
You're really annoying.
أنت مزعج حقا.
Why do you keep making me conscious of you?
لماذا تستمر في جعلني واعيا بك؟
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
You're so annoying.
أنت مزعجة جدًا.
Don't you have any other characters?
هل ليس لديك أي شخصيات أخرى؟
This won't work.
هذا لن ينجح.
I don't...
أنا لا...
Why does this character want to marry her when he finds her so annoying?
لماذا تريد هذه الشخصية الزواج منها عندما تجدها مزعجة للغاية؟
That's because he can't recognize his feelings.
هذا لأنه لا يستطيع التعرف على مشاعره.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
If he doesn't even know what he's feeling,
إذا كان لا يعرف حتى ما يشعر به،
why would he confess his love?
لماذا يعترف بحبه؟
Are you stupid?
هل انت غبي؟
Darn it.
لعنة عليك.
You're worried about how you feel, but you can't ask them.
أنت قلق بشأن ما تشعر به، ولكن لا يمكنك أن تسألهم.
Yet, you want to keep them by your side.
ومع ذلك، فأنت تريد الاحتفاظ بهم بجانبك.
But then you're in a dilemma.
ولكن حينها ستقع في مأزق.
Then you'd raise your voice 'cause you're scared.
ثم ترفع صوتك لأنك خائف.
Scared? This man is way scarier.
خائف؟ هذا الرجل مخيف جدًا.
He's a gangster boss!
إنه زعيم العصابات!
That identity means nothing.
هذه الهوية لا تعني شيئا.
This man
هذا الرجل
would rather be stabbed than be rejected.
يفضل أن يُطعن على أن يُرفض.
What does that mean?
ماذا يعني ذلك؟
It's the same in the real world, too.
إنه نفس الشيء في العالم الحقيقي أيضًا.
It's not like he's a coward.
إنه ليس جبانًا.
He is a coward.
إنه جبان.
A very timid
خجول جدا
scaredy-cat.
قطة خائفة.
Then he's just an idiot.
إذن فهو مجرد أحمق.
He is an idiot, that's right.
إنه أحمق، هذا صحيح.
Intimidated by his own emotions.
خائفًا من مشاعره الخاصة.
I'm so sad.
أنا حزين جداً.
No, or do I feel a little suffocated?
لا، أم أنني أشعر بالاختناق قليلاً؟
Can you read this man's lines for me?
هل يمكنك أن تقرأ لي سطور هذا الرجل؟
Why?
لماذا؟
I think I need to hear you say it to understand.
أعتقد أنني بحاجة إلى سماعك تقول ذلك لفهمه.
Ha Keumpoop, you're really getting the most out of your red bean porridge.
ها كومبوب، أنت حقا تحصل على أقصى استفادة من عصيدة الفاصوليا الحمراء الخاصة بك.
You're really annoying.
أنت مزعج حقا.
Why do you keep making me conscious of you?
لماذا تستمر في جعلني واعيا بك؟
I can't tell if this is a confession or a threat.
لا أستطيع أن أقول إذا كان هذا اعترافًا أم تهديدًا.
Who are you calling a kid?
من تنادي الطفل؟
Are you going to keep making me conscious of you?
هل ستستمر في جعلني واعيًا بك؟
I found it!
لقد وجدته!
[Ha Keumbok]
[في كومبوك]